<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Asset Management on</title><link>/docs/legal-hub/compliance/asset-management/</link><description>Recent content in Asset Management on</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 14:19:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/docs/legal-hub/compliance/asset-management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Laptop Management</title><link>/docs/legal-hub/compliance/asset-management/laptop-management/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 14:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/legal-hub/compliance/asset-management/laptop-management/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="this-is-a-controlled-document">This is a Controlled Document&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>In line with GitLab’s regulatory obligations, changes to controlled documents must be approved or merged by a code owner. All contributions are welcome and encouraged.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="purpose">Purpose&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This page displays different pieces of information surrounding GitLab laptop procurement and management.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="scope">Scope&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>At GitLab, we use centralized laptop management for company issued devices. If you are in possession of a company issued laptop, the details below apply to you. However, not all endpoint management technologies GitLab deploys will be required for Apple, Linux, and Windows laptops. Some technologies may be specific to the hardware platform or operating system.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Portable Appliance Testing Policy</title><link>/docs/legal-hub/compliance/asset-management/portable-appliance-testing-policy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 22:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/legal-hub/compliance/asset-management/portable-appliance-testing-policy/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Equipment Policy</title><link>/docs/legal-hub/compliance/asset-management/equipment-policy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 21:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/legal-hub/compliance/asset-management/equipment-policy/</guid><description/></item><item><title>It Asset Management</title><link>/docs/legal-hub/compliance/asset-management/it-asset-management/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 21:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/legal-hub/compliance/asset-management/it-asset-management/</guid><description>&lt;p>Green Orbit Digital IT Asset Management Policy&lt;/p>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>Introduction&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;p>IT Asset Management (ITAM) at Green Orbit Digital is a key process for efficiently and securely managing technology resources throughout their lifecycle. This guidance outlines the procedures for acquiring, maintaining, and disposing of IT assets. It ensures that assets are properly tracked, managed, and utilised to support business operations while minimising security risks, costs, and environmental impact.&lt;/p>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>Purpose&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;p>The purpose of this IT Asset Management guidance is to:&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Local Purchasing And Hiring Policy</title><link>/docs/legal-hub/compliance/asset-management/local-purchasing-and-hiring-policy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 21:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/legal-hub/compliance/asset-management/local-purchasing-and-hiring-policy/</guid><description>&lt;p>Green Orbit Digital is committed to supporting local economic development through strategic local purchasing and hiring practices. This policy outlines our approach to prioritizing local suppliers and talent while maintaining our high standards for quality and sustainability.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="1-purpose-and-scope">1. Purpose and Scope&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This policy applies to all procurement activities and hiring processes within Green Orbit Digital. It aims to maximize our positive impact on local communities while ensuring business efficiency and compliance with our sustainability goals.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Fixed Assets Tracking</title><link>/docs/legal-hub/compliance/asset-management/fixed-assets-tracking/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 17:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/legal-hub/compliance/asset-management/fixed-assets-tracking/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="fixed-assets-tracking-policy">Fixed Assets Tracking Policy&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="1-purpose-and-scope">1. Purpose and Scope&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This policy establishes guidelines for tracking and managing fixed assets at Green Orbit Digital to ensure proper accountability, maintenance, and financial control of company assets.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="2-asset-definition-and-classification">2. Asset Definition and Classification&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Fixed assets are defined as tangible items owned by Green Orbit Digital that have a useful life of more than one year. These include but are not limited to equipment, furniture, vehicles, and electronic devices.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>General Purchasing Guidelines</title><link>/docs/legal-hub/compliance/asset-management/general-purchasing-guidelines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/legal-hub/compliance/asset-management/general-purchasing-guidelines/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="general-purchasing-guidelines">General Purchasing Guidelines&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="core-principles">Core Principles&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Before making any purchase, carefully consider these key factors:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Performance vs Impact: Evaluate both the performance of items against their social and environmental impact and cost&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Supplier Compliance: Ensure all suppliers comply with our Supplier Code of Conduct&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Environmental Preference: Prioritize products that demonstrate resource efficiency and environmental responsibility&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h2 id="procurement-process">Procurement Process&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Follow these steps for all purchases:&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="1-need-assessment">1. Need Assessment&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Clearly identify and justify the business need&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>